https://www.luxfermeltechnologies.com/cookie-policy/

Privacy and Cookies - Luxfer MEL Technologies
Skip to content
Contact us
TwitterLinkedInYouTube
Search for:
Search for:
Home
About us
Markets
AerospaceAircraft InteriorsCeramicsDrive TrainEnginesAutomotiveAutomotive CatalysisCeramicsCommerical AutomotiveMotorsportCatalysisAutomotive CatalysisIndustrial CatalysisCeramicsTin OxideZirconium OxidesCoatings and SolutionsDefenseAdsorbent MaterialsMan-Portable MaterialsExtruded and Forging MagnesiumExtruded MagnesiumForging BilletHealthcareResorbable MagnesiumCeramicsOil and GasCareers
Life at LuxferApprentices and GraduatesApply nowNews
Downloads
Contact us
Search for:
Home
About us
Markets
AerospaceAircraft InteriorsCeramicsDrive TrainEnginesAutomotiveAutomotive CatalysisCeramicsCommerical AutomotiveMotorsportCatalysisAutomotive CatalysisIndustrial CatalysisCeramicsTin OxideZirconium OxidesCoatings and SolutionsDefenseAdsorbent MaterialsMan-Portable MaterialsExtruded and Forging MagnesiumExtruded MagnesiumForging BilletHealthcareResorbable MagnesiumCeramicsOil and GasCareers
Life at LuxferApprentices and GraduatesApply nowNews
Downloads
Contact us
Home
About us
Markets
AerospaceAircraft InteriorsCeramicsDrive TrainEnginesAutomotiveAutomotive CatalysisCeramicsCommerical AutomotiveMotorsportCatalysisAutomotive CatalysisIndustrial CatalysisCeramicsTin OxideZirconium OxidesCoatings and SolutionsDefenseAdsorbent MaterialsMan-Portable MaterialsExtruded and Forging MagnesiumExtruded MagnesiumForging BilletHealthcareResorbable MagnesiumCeramicsOil and GasCareers
Life at LuxferApprentices and GraduatesApply nowNews
Downloads
Contact us
Search for:
Privacy and CookiesJamie2018-10-17T13:20:10+00:00
Privacy and Cookies
Cookie policy
This cookie policy explains what cookies are and how we use them on our website. You should read this policy so you can understand what type of cookies we use, the information we collect using the cookies and how that information is used. By using our website, you are agreeing that we can use cookies in accordance with this policy.
Our cookie and privacy policy also applies to our sub-domain serviceandinnovationinmagnesium.com
What are cookies?
Cookies are files which contain a small amount of information. Cookies are stored on the browser or hard drive of your computer or device.
How do we use cookies?
We use cookies to distinguish you from other users of our website and to provide a browsing experience that is unique to you.
What type of cookies do we use?
Cookies can be in the form of session cookies or persistent cookies. Session cookies are deleted from your computer or device when you close your web-browser. Persistent cookies will remain stored on your computer or device until deleted or until they reach their expiry date. We use the following cookies:
Analytical/performance cookies – These cookies allow us to recognise and count the number of visitors to our website and to see how visitors move around when they are using it. This helps us to improve the way our website works, for example, by ensuring that users find what they are looking for easily.
Targeting cookies – These cookies record your visit to our website, the pages you have visited and the links you have followed. We will use this information to make our website and the advertising displayed on it more relevant to your interests. We may also share this information with third parties for this purpose. These cookies allow you to share and send information to other websites.
What kind of information do we collect by using cookies?
When you visit our website, we may automatically collect the following types of information from you: date you access the page, time of access, which pages you have accessed. Additionally, This website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. (“Google”). Google Analytics uses “cookies”, which are text files placed on your computer, to help the website analyse how users use the site. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States.
In case IP-anonymization is activated on this website, your IP address will be truncated within the area of Member States of the European Union or other parties to the Agreement on the European Economic Area. Only in exceptional cases the whole IP address will be first transferred to a Google server in the USA and truncated there. The IP-anonymization is active on this website. Google will use this information on behalf of the operator of this website for the purpose of evaluating your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity for website operators and providing them other services relating to website activity and internet usage. The IP-address, that your Browser conveys within the scope of Google Analytics, will not be associated with any other data held by Google.
How do you block cookies?
Most browsers allow you to refuse cookies. You may block our cookies by activating the setting on your browser that allows you to refuse the setting of all or some cookies. You can find out more about cookies and how to delete and control them on www.aboutcookies.org or click help in your browser menu.
If you block our use of cookies, you may be unable to access certain areas of our website and certain functions and pages will not work in the usual way.
You can also opt-out from being tracked by Google Analytics with effect for the future by downloading and installing Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Addon for your current web browser: http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en.
How Luxfer MEL Technologies can change the Cookie Policy
We may update this policy from time to time. Changes in technology, legislation and authorities’ guidance may require us to inform you of the activities we undertake where it affects your privacy rights. You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are familiar with any changes.
Privacy policy
Luxfer MEL Technologies is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This Privacy Policy applies to the Luxfer MEL Technologies website and governs data collection and usage. By using the Luxfer MEL Technologies website, you consent to the data practices described in this policy.
Collection of your personal information
Luxfer MEL Technologies collects personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address or telephone number.
There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by Luxfer MEL Technologies. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used by Luxfer MEL Technologies for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Luxfer MEL Technologies website.
Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through Luxfer MEL Technologies public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others. Note: Luxfer MEL Technologies does not read any of your private online communications.
Luxfer MEL Technologies encourages you to review the privacy policies of websites you choose to link to from Luxfer MEL Technologies so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. Luxfer MEL Technologies is not responsible for the privacy policies or other content on websites outside of the Luxfer MEL Technologies and Luxfer MEL Technologies family of websites.
Use of your personal information
Luxfer MEL Technologies collects and uses your personal information to operate the Luxfer MEL Technologies website and deliver the services you have requested. Luxfer MEL Technologies also uses your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Luxfer MEL Technologies and its affiliates. Luxfer MEL Technologies may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.
Luxfer MEL Technologies does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. Luxfer MEL Technologies may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, Luxfer MEL Technologies may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Luxfer MEL Technologies and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.
Luxfer MEL Technologies does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.
Luxfer MEL Technologies keeps track of the websites and pages our customers visit within Luxfer MEL Technologies in order to determine what Luxfer MEL Technologies services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within Luxfer MEL Technologies to customers whose behaviour indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.
Luxfer MEL Technologies websites will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Luxfer MEL Technologies or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Luxfer MEL Technologies; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Luxfer MEL Technologies, or the public.
Security of your personal information
Luxfer MEL Technologies secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. Luxfer MEL Technologies secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.
Changes to this policy
Luxfer MEL Technologies will occasionally update this Privacy Policy to reflect company and customer feedback. Luxfer MEL Technologies encourages you to periodically review this Policy to be informed of how Luxfer MEL Technologies is protecting your information.
Contact information
Luxfer MEL Technologies welcomes your comments regarding this Privacy Policy. If you believe that Luxfer MEL Technologies has not adhered to this Policy, please contact us. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
For United States
For UK and Rest of the World
Zirconium
Luxfer MEL Technologies
500 Barbertown Point Breeze Road
Flemington, NJ 08822
Office: +1 908 782 5800
E: LMT.Customerservice-Flemington@luxfer.com
This site uses cookies:
Find out more.Okay, thank you
Go to Top
